const seedquestions = [
  {
    question:
      "The format of this cricket variant is characterized by matches lasting a single day.",
    answer: "What is One Day International (ODI) cricket?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      'This legendary Australian cricketer is often referred to as "The Don."',
    answer: "Who is Don Bradman?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question: 'The term "LBW" in cricket stands for this.',
    answer: "What is Leg Before Wicket?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The maximum number of runs a batsman can score off a single ball in a standard game.",
    answer: "What is six?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In cricket, this term refers to a bowler taking three wickets with three consecutive deliveries.",
    answer: "What is a hat-trick?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question: "The international governing body for cricket.",
    answer: "What is the International Cricket Council (ICC)?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Ashes is a historic Test cricket series played between England and this country.",
    answer: "What is Australia?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The longest format of the game, known for matches lasting up to five days.",
    answer: "What is Test cricket?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      'The famous Indian cricketer nicknamed "Little Master" for his incredible batting skills.',
    answer: "Who is Sachin Tendulkar?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The protective gear worn by a batsman, including gloves and leg pads.",
    answer: "What is cricket gear?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "In limited-overs cricket, a fielding restriction where only a certain number of fielders are allowed outside the 30-yard circle.",
    answer: "What is Powerplay?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The international T20 tournament where franchises like Mumbai Indians and Chennai Super Kings compete.",
    answer: "What is the Indian Premier League (IPL)?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "This West Indian cricketer is known for hitting the first-ever six in international cricket.",
    answer: "Who is Sir Garfield Sobers?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The type of delivery in which the bowler imparts spin to the ball using their fingers.",
    answer: "What is a spin delivery?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a batsman being dismissed without scoring any runs.",
    answer: "What is a duck?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question: "The cricket World Cup is held in this format every four years.",
    answer: "What is One Day International (ODI)?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term used for a match in which both teams score the same number of runs, resulting in a tie.",
    answer: "What is a tie?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The first cricket format to feature colored clothing and floodlights for day-night matches.",
    answer: "What is One Day International (ODI)?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The highest individual score by a batsman in a Test match, achieved by Brian Lara.",
    answer: "What is 400 not out?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The cricketing term for a bowler taking five wickets in a single innings.",
    answer: "What is a five-wicket haul?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Indian cricketer known as the 'Captain Cool' for his calm demeanor on the field.",
    answer: "Who is Mahendra Singh Dhoni?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The cricketing term for a delivery that pitches on the leg side and swings towards the off side.",
    answer: "What is an outswinger?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The iconic Australian cricket ground known as the 'Gabbatoir' for its strong home team record.",
    answer: "What is the Gabba?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question: "The term for a bowler taking ten wickets in a single innings.",
    answer: "What is a ten-wicket haul?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The West Indian cricketer who holds the record for the fastest century in T20 internationals.",
    answer: "Who is Chris Gayle?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The cricketing term for a ball that is bowled without bouncing on the pitch.",
    answer: "What is a full toss?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The English cricketer known for his aggressive style and hitting six sixes in an over.",
    answer: "Who is Yuvraj Singh?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a match where a team wins without the opposing team having batted in the second innings.",
    answer: "What is a innings victory?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The cricketing term for a batsman who scores runs quickly and aggressively.",
    answer: "What is a hard-hitter?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Australian cricketer known as 'Pigeon' for his accurate and deadly fast bowling.",
    answer: "Who is Glenn McGrath?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The format of cricket known for its fast-paced and entertaining nature, typically lasting around three hours.",
    answer: "What is Twenty20 (T20) cricket?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Indian cricketer who holds the record for the highest individual score in Test cricket as of 2022.",
    answer: "Who is Virender Sehwag?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a ball that is delivered by a spinner with a deceptive trajectory.",
    answer: "What is a doosra?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The English cricketer who was the first woman to score 6000 runs in One Day Internationals.",
    answer: "Who is Charlotte Edwards?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The number of overs in a standard One Day International (ODI) cricket match.",
    answer: "What is 50 overs?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a situation where a batsman is not out at the end of a team's innings.",
    answer: "What is stranded?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Pakistani cricketer who is the fastest to reach 1000 runs in T20 internationals.",
    answer: "Who is Babar Azam?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The cricketing term for a ball that deviates sharply off the pitch due to seam movement.",
    answer: "What is seam bowling?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Sri Lankan cricketer who is the highest run-scorer in One Day Internationals (ODIs).",
    answer: "Who is Kumar Sangakkara?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a situation where a batsman is dismissed without facing a legal delivery.",
    answer: "What is hit wicket?",
    topic: "Cricket",
  },
  {
    question:
      "This Argentine soccer legend, often compared to Pele, is known for his incredible dribbling skills and the 'Hand of God' incident.",
    answer: "Who is Diego Maradona?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question: "The country that has won the most FIFA World Cup titles.",
    answer: "What is Brazil?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a situation where a player scores three goals in a single game.",
    answer: "What is a hat-trick?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question: "The English soccer club with the nickname 'Red Devils.'",
    answer: "What is Manchester United?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The highest goal scorer in the history of FIFA World Cup tournaments.",
    answer: "Who is Miroslav Klose?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The annual individual award given to the best male soccer player in the world.",
    answer: "What is the FIFA Ballon d'Or?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The South American country where the soccer stadium 'Maracan√£' is located.",
    answer: "What is Brazil?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a soccer match that ends with both teams having scored an equal number of goals.",
    answer: "What is a draw?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Italian soccer club known for its defensive prowess and nicknamed 'The Old Lady.'",
    answer: "What is Juventus?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The English striker who is the all-time top scorer for the England national football team.",
    answer: "Who is Wayne Rooney?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a soccer match where both teams score the same number of goals.",
    answer: "What is a draw?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Portuguese soccer player who has won multiple FIFA Ballon d'Or awards.",
    answer: "Who is Cristiano Ronaldo?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question: "The African country that won the FIFA World Cup in 2010.",
    answer: "What is South Africa?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The German soccer club that won the UEFA Champions League in the 2020-2021 season.",
    answer: "What is Bayern Munich?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a player who primarily plays as a central attacking midfielder.",
    answer: "What is a number 10?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Spanish soccer club that plays its home matches at the Camp Nou stadium.",
    answer: "What is FC Barcelona?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The French soccer player who won the 1998 FIFA World Cup and 2000 UEFA European Championship.",
    answer: "Who is Zinedine Zidane?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a soccer match that goes into extra time after ending in a draw.",
    answer: "What is extra time?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Italian goalkeeper known for his incredible saves and nicknamed 'Superman.'",
    answer: "Who is Gianluigi Buffon?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The South American soccer player who won the FIFA World Player of the Century award.",
    answer: "Who is Pel√©?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a soccer match where a team does not concede any goals.",
    answer: "What is a clean sheet?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Dutch soccer player known for his creative midfield skills and nicknamed 'The Flying Dutchman.'",
    answer: "Who is Johan Cruyff?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The soccer tournament held every four years and contested by national teams from around the world.",
    answer: "What is the FIFA World Cup?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question: "The English soccer club with the nickname 'The Gunners.'",
    answer: "What is Arsenal?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a player who primarily plays as a central defender.",
    answer: "What is a center-back?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Argentine soccer player known for his incredible goal-scoring record and nicknamed 'The Atomic Flea.'",
    answer: "Who is Lionel Messi?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Italian soccer player known for his defensive skills and nicknamed 'Il Capitano.'",
    answer: "Who is Paolo Maldini?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a player who primarily plays as a central midfielder.",
    answer: "What is a midfielder?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Brazilian soccer player known for his flair, skill, and nicknamed 'The Magician.'",
    answer: "Who is Ronaldinho?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question: "The European country that hosted the UEFA Euro 2020 tournament.",
    answer: "What is multiple countries? (12 host cities)",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a soccer match where a team wins without conceding any goals.",
    answer: "What is a shutout?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The German soccer player known for his powerful shots and free-kick expertise.",
    answer: "Who is Thomas M√ºller?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Spanish soccer club that won three consecutive UEFA Champions League titles from 2016 to 2018.",
    answer: "What is Real Madrid?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a soccer match where both teams score at least one goal.",
    answer: "What is a scored draw?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The French soccer player who won the 1998 FIFA World Cup and later became a successful manager.",
    answer: "Who is Didier Deschamps?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Italian soccer player known for his precise passing and vision, nicknamed 'The Architect.'",
    answer: "Who is Andrea Pirlo?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a soccer match where both teams score an equal number of goals and no winner is declared.",
    answer: "What is a draw?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Spanish soccer player known for his prolific goal-scoring and nicknamed 'El Ni√±o.'",
    answer: "Who is Fernando Torres?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a soccer match where a team wins by a margin of three goals.",
    answer: "What is a three-goal victory?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Portuguese soccer player known for his skillful dribbling and nicknamed 'O Magico.'",
    answer: "Who is Ricardo Quaresma?",
    topic: "Soccer",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The sport in which players use a shuttlecock and racquets to hit it over a net.",
    answer: "What is badminton?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question: "The country where badminton originated and gained popularity.",
    answer: "What is England?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a shot that is hit softly and lands just over the net in badminton.",
    answer: "What is a drop shot?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The maximum number of players on a badminton court during a doubles match.",
    answer: "What is 4?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The scoring system used in badminton, where games are played to 21 points.",
    answer: "What is rally scoring?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a shot in badminton where the shuttle is hit forcefully downward into the opponent's court.",
    answer: "What is a smash?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The piece of equipment used in badminton that is hit back and forth over the net.",
    answer: "What is a shuttlecock?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question: "The player who serves first in a badminton match.",
    answer: "What is the side that wins the coin toss or spin?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a shot in badminton where the shuttle is hit just above the net and drops sharply over.",
    answer: "What is a net shot?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The governing body for international badminton competitions, including the Olympics.",
    answer: "What is the Badminton World Federation (BWF)?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Indian badminton player who won the silver medal in the women's singles at the 2016 Olympics.",
    answer: "Who is P.V. Sindhu?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a shot that is hit softly and falls just over the net in badminton.",
    answer: "What is a drop shot?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Swedish badminton player known for his agility and considered one of the greatest of all time.",
    answer: "Who is Jan O. Jorgensen?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The part of the badminton court where serves must land during a game.",
    answer: "What is the diagonal service court?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a continuous and fast exchange of shots in badminton.",
    answer: "What is a rally?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The badminton tournament considered the most prestigious in the world.",
    answer: "What is the All England Open Badminton Championships?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a shot that is hit with a slicing motion in badminton.",
    answer: "What is a slice shot?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Chinese badminton player known as 'Super Dan' and considered one of the greatest players in history.",
    answer: "Who is Lin Dan?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The material used to make the skirt of a shuttlecock in professional badminton.",
    answer: "What is feathers (goose feathers)?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a shot in badminton where the shuttle is hit with a quick wrist movement.",
    answer: "What is a flick?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Malaysian badminton player known as the 'Dato' Lee Chong Wei' and considered one of the greatest singles players.",
    answer: "Who is Lee Chong Wei?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a shot in badminton where the shuttle is hit just above the net and drops sharply over.",
    answer: "What is a net shot?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The country that has historically dominated international badminton, especially in men's and women's singles.",
    answer: "What is China?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The badminton player who won the most Olympic gold medals in mixed doubles, partnering with Zhang Nan.",
    answer: "Who is Zhao Yunlei?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a shot in badminton where the shuttle travels low and parallel to the net.",
    answer: "What is a drive?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Indonesian badminton player known for his powerful jump smash and considered one of the best in men's singles.",
    answer: "Who is Taufik Hidayat?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a situation where a badminton match reaches a score of 29-29, requiring a two-point lead to win.",
    answer: "What is sudden death or golden point?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Indian badminton player known as the 'Golden Girl' and the first Indian woman to win an Olympic silver medal in badminton.",
    answer: "Who is P.V. Sindhu?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The part of a badminton court that is not part of the playing area and is often out of bounds.",
    answer: "What is the out-of-bounds area?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The badminton player known for popularizing the use of the backhand overhead smash.",
    answer: "Who is Rudy Hartono?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a badminton shot that involves a deceptive change of direction, often used in doubles play.",
    answer: "What is a flick serve?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Danish badminton player known for his technical skills and success in men's singles.",
    answer: "Who is Viktor Axelsen?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a shot in badminton where the shuttle is hit downward at an angle, making it difficult for the opponent to return.",
    answer: "What is a crosscourt smash?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The badminton tournament that is part of the BWF Super Series and features top players from around the world.",
    answer: "What is the All England Open Badminton Championships?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Indian badminton player who won the gold medal at the 2018 Commonwealth Games in women's singles.",
    answer: "Who is Saina Nehwal?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a shot in badminton where the shuttle is hit softly and falls just over the net.",
    answer: "What is a drop shot?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The shuttlecock used in professional badminton that is made from synthetic materials.",
    answer: "What is a nylon shuttlecock?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The badminton player who won the most Olympic gold medals in women's doubles, partnering with Tang Jinhua.",
    answer: "Who is Yu Yang?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a shot in badminton where the shuttle is hit high and deep into the opponent's court.",
    answer: "What is a clear?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The badminton player known for his exceptional speed and agility, earning him the nickname 'Super Dan.'",
    answer: "Who is Lin Dan?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a badminton shot where the shuttle is hit downward with force, usually aimed at the opponent's body.",
    answer: "What is a smash?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The badminton player who holds the record for the fastest smash in professional badminton.",
    answer: "Who is Fu Haifeng?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The governing body for international badminton competitions and events.",
    answer: "What is the Badminton World Federation (BWF)?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a shot in badminton where the shuttle is hit over the opponent's head and lands deep in their court.",
    answer: "What is a lob?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Malaysian badminton player known for his successful career in men's singles and Olympic silver medal in 2016.",
    answer: "Who is Lee Chong Wei?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Chinese badminton player who won the gold medal in women's singles at the 2012 Olympics.",
    answer: "Who is Li Xuerui?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a situation in badminton where the server's score is even.",
    answer: "What is an even score?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Indian badminton player who won the silver medal in women's singles at the 2016 Olympics.",
    answer: "Who is P.V. Sindhu?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The part of a badminton court where the serve must land during a singles match.",
    answer: "What is the long service court?",
    topic: "Badminton",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The international multi-sport event held every four years, bringing together athletes from around the world.",
    answer: "What are the Olympic Games?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The city where the first modern Olympic Games were held in 1896.",
    answer: "What is Athens?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic symbol featuring five interlocked rings representing the continents of the world.",
    answer: "What are the Olympic rings?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The number of rings on the Olympic flag, each representing a different continent.",
    answer: "What is five?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for the cessation of hostilities during the Olympic Games to ensure safe travel for athletes and spectators.",
    answer: "What is the Olympic Truce?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question: "The country that has hosted the most Summer Olympic Games.",
    answer: "What is the United States?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Greek goddess of victory, whose statue is often associated with the Olympics.",
    answer: "Who is Nike?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question: "The year when the first Winter Olympic Games were held.",
    answer: "What is 1924?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic Games were not held in this number of Olympiads during the 20th century due to World Wars.",
    answer: "What is three?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for the flame that is lit at Olympia and brought to the host city of the Olympics.",
    answer: "What is the Olympic flame?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient stadium in Olympia where the Olympic flame is traditionally lit.",
    answer: "What is the Stadium at Olympia?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The country that has won the most total Olympic medals in the history of the Summer and Winter Games combined.",
    answer: "What is the United States?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a tie or draw in a competition, often used in the elimination rounds of Olympic events.",
    answer: "What is a deadlock?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The year when the Summer and Winter Olympic Games were held in the same year for the first time.",
    answer: "What is 1992?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question: "The host city of the 2024 Summer Olympics.",
    answer: "What is Paris?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic event that involves sliding down a narrow, twisting, banked ice track in a small, flat sled.",
    answer: "What is the luge?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for an athlete who competes in both the Summer and Winter Olympic Games.",
    answer: "What is a dual Olympian?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question: "The host city of the 2022 Winter Olympics.",
    answer: "What is Beijing?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic event that involves skiing and shooting, testing both physical and marksmanship skills.",
    answer: "What is the biathlon?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a formal declaration by the host city that it wants to bid to host the Olympic Games.",
    answer: "What is an Olympic bid?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question: "The year when the first Summer Paralympic Games were held.",
    answer: "What is 1960?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic event that involves performing acrobatics and artistic routines on a horizontal bar, rings, and other apparatus.",
    answer: "What is gymnastics?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question: "The host city of the 2028 Summer Olympics.",
    answer: "What is Los Angeles?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic event that involves racing in a small, one- or two-person boat using paddles.",
    answer: "What is canoe sprint?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for an Olympic athlete who competes in multiple sports.",
    answer: "What is a multi-sport athlete?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The country that boycotted the 1980 Summer Olympics in protest of the Soviet invasion of Afghanistan.",
    answer: "What is the United States?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic event that involves figure skaters performing jumps, spins, and other intricate movements on ice.",
    answer: "What is figure skating?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic Games were canceled in this number of Olympiads during the 20th century due to World Wars.",
    answer: "What is three?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for the ceremony where Olympic medals are awarded to the winning athletes.",
    answer: "What is the medal ceremony?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question: "The host city of the 2032 Summer Olympics.",
    answer: "What is Brisbane?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic event that involves athletes competing in a variety of track and field events.",
    answer: "What is the decathlon?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Greek island that was the birthplace of the ancient Olympic Games.",
    answer: "What is Olympia?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The number of gold medals won by swimmer Michael Phelps in a single Olympic Games, setting a record.",
    answer: "What is eight?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for the final event of the Olympic Games, featuring the extinguishing of the Olympic flame.",
    answer: "What is the closing ceremony?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic event that involves competitors skiing and then shooting at targets with a rifle.",
    answer: "What is the biathlon?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question: "The number of Olympic rings that are colored blue.",
    answer: "What is one?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for the opening ceremony of the Olympic Games, symbolizing the beginning of the event.",
    answer: "What is the opening ceremony?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question: "The year when the first Youth Olympic Games were held.",
    answer: "What is 2010?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic event that involves riders performing tricks and jumps on a BMX bicycle.",
    answer: "What is BMX freestyle?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic event that involves athletes skiing and then jumping off a ramp.",
    answer: "What is Nordic combined?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question: "The year when the first Paralympic Winter Games were held.",
    answer: "What is 1976?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic event that involves athletes competing in various gymnastic disciplines, including floor exercises and the pommel horse.",
    answer: "What is artistic gymnastics?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question: "The host city of the 2026 Winter Olympics.",
    answer: "What is Milan-Cortina?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic event that involves athletes swimming, cycling, and running in succession.",
    answer: "What is the triathlon?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for a situation where a country voluntarily decides not to participate in the Olympic Games as a form of protest.",
    answer: "What is an Olympic boycott?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question: "The first modern Olympics included this number of sports.",
    answer: "What is nine?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic event that involves athletes shooting at targets with a pistol or rifle.",
    answer: "What is shooting?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Olympic event that involves athletes performing routines on ice with jumps, spins, and lifts.",
    answer: "What is pair figure skating?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The term for an Olympic event where competitors perform tricks and stunts on a snowboard.",
    answer: "What is snowboard freestyle?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question: "The host city of the 2030 Winter Olympics.",
    answer: "What is Salt Lake City?",
    topic: "Olympics",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The animated movie featuring a young mermaid who dreams of living on land.",
    answer: "What is The Little Mermaid?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The lion cub who becomes the king of the Pride Lands in Disney's 'The Lion King.'",
    answer: "Who is Simba?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The animated film where a street-smart thief teams up with a princess and a magical genie.",
    answer: "What is Aladdin?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question: "The Disney-Pixar movie about a clownfish searching for his son.",
    answer: "What is Finding Nemo?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The tale of a wooden boy who dreams of becoming a real boy, brought to life by a magical fairy.",
    answer: "What is Pinocchio?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Disney movie where a young girl falls down a rabbit hole and enters a whimsical world.",
    answer: "What is Alice in Wonderland?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The animated film featuring a young Chinese woman disguising herself as a man to take her father's place in the army.",
    answer: "What is Mulan?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The enchanted castle where Belle becomes a prisoner in 'Beauty and the Beast.'",
    answer: "What is the Beast's Castle?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Pixar movie that follows the adventures of a superhero family with superpowers.",
    answer: "What is The Incredibles?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Disney film where a young deer learns important life lessons from his friends Thumper and Flower.",
    answer: "What is Bambi?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The animated movie set in the city of Zootopia, where a bunny teams up with a sly fox to solve a mystery.",
    answer: "What is Zootopia?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The classic Disney movie featuring princess Aurora, Maleficent, and a spinning wheel curse.",
    answer: "What is Sleeping Beauty?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Pixar film that explores the emotions inside the mind of a young girl named Riley.",
    answer: "What is Inside Out?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Disney movie where a wooden marionette is brought to life by the Blue Fairy.",
    answer: "What is Pinocchio?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Disney-Pixar movie featuring a robot named WALL-E who falls in love and embarks on a space adventure.",
    answer: "What is WALL-E?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The animated film where a young girl befriends seven dwarfs and takes on an evil queen.",
    answer: "What is Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Disney-Pixar movie where an old man ties thousands of balloons to his house and flies to South America.",
    answer: "What is Up?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Disney movie about a young lion cub who must reclaim his throne from his evil uncle Scar.",
    answer: "What is The Lion King?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Disney film where Cinderella's magical night at the ball changes her life.",
    answer: "What is Cinderella?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Pixar movie where toys come to life when humans are not around.",
    answer: "What is Toy Story?",
    topic: "Disney Movies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The first Marvel Cinematic Universe (MCU) film, released in 2008, featuring Tony Stark as Iron Man.",
    answer: "What is Iron Man?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The powerful artifact that is central to many Marvel movies, including 'The Avengers' and 'Guardians of the Galaxy.'",
    answer: "What is the Tesseract?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where the Norse god Thor wields his enchanted hammer, Mjolnir.",
    answer: "What is Thor?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The group of superheroes who come together to form a team in Marvel's 'The Avengers.'",
    answer: "What is the Avengers?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The main antagonist in 'Black Panther,' ruling the fictional African nation of Wakanda.",
    answer: "Who is Killmonger?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where the sorcerer Stephen Strange learns the mystic arts to become the Sorcerer Supreme.",
    answer: "What is Doctor Strange?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The powerful, reality-altering gem featured in Marvel movies, sought after by Thanos.",
    answer: "What is the Reality Stone?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The actor who portrayed the character Deadpool in the Marvel movie 'Deadpool.'",
    answer: "Who is Ryan Reynolds?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where Tony Stark builds a suit of armor to escape captivity and fights against terrorists.",
    answer: "What is Iron Man?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The sentient android created by Tony Stark and Bruce Banner, featured in 'Avengers: Age of Ultron.'",
    answer: "Who is Ultron?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The iconic shield carried by Captain America, made of vibranium, in Marvel movies.",
    answer: "What is the vibranium shield?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where the Guardians of the Galaxy team up to protect a powerful orb from falling into the wrong hands.",
    answer: "What is Guardians of the Galaxy?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who becomes the Winter Soldier in Marvel movies after being presumed dead in World War II.",
    answer: "Who is Bucky Barnes?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The fictional metal alloy that is stronger than adamantium, found in the Black Panther's suit.",
    answer: "What is vibranium?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where Scott Lang takes on the role of Ant-Man, with the ability to shrink in size.",
    answer: "What is Ant-Man?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The powerful villain in 'Avengers: Infinity War' who seeks to collect all six Infinity Stones.",
    answer: "Who is Thanos?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The superhero in Marvel movies who can change size and communicate with ants.",
    answer: "Who is Ant-Man?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where the hero T'Challa returns to Wakanda to take the throne as king.",
    answer: "What is Black Panther?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The organization led by Nick Fury that recruits superheroes in Marvel's 'The Avengers.'",
    answer: "What is S.H.I.E.L.D.?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character in Marvel movies known for his archery skills and wielding a bow and arrow.",
    answer: "Who is Hawkeye?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie that explores the origin of the character Carol Danvers, who becomes Captain Marvel.",
    answer: "What is Captain Marvel?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The powerful alien artifact that serves as the primary focus of 'Avengers: Endgame.'",
    answer: "What is the Quantum Realm?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where Peter Parker receives mentorship from Tony Stark and battles the Vulture.",
    answer: "What is Spider-Man: Homecoming?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The villain in 'Black Panther' who challenges T'Challa for the throne of Wakanda.",
    answer: "Who is Erik Killmonger?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The actor who plays Tony Stark/Iron Man in the Marvel Cinematic Universe.",
    answer: "Who is Robert Downey Jr.?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where the hero Peter Quill, also known as Star-Lord, forms the Guardians of the Galaxy.",
    answer: "What is Guardians of the Galaxy?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The superhero in Marvel movies who possesses super strength, enhanced agility, and a vibranium shield.",
    answer: "Who is Captain America?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where Doctor Strange faces the interdimensional entity known as Dormammu.",
    answer: "What is Doctor Strange?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character in Marvel movies who is the Norse god of mischief and brother to Thor.",
    answer: "Who is Loki?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where the hero T'Challa defends his throne and country from various adversaries.",
    answer: "What is Black Panther?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The artifact that houses the Mind Stone and grants superhuman abilities to certain characters in Marvel movies.",
    answer: "What is the Scepter?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character in Marvel movies who is a brilliant scientist, billionaire, and philanthropist, also known as Iron Man.",
    answer: "Who is Tony Stark?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where the hero Scott Lang, also known as Ant-Man, teams up with the Wasp.",
    answer: "What is Ant-Man and The Wasp?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie that explores the backstory of Natasha Romanoff, also known as Black Widow.",
    answer: "What is Black Widow?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The extraterrestrial race featured in 'Guardians of the Galaxy' known for their literal interpretations.",
    answer: "What are the Kree?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character in Marvel movies who is a skilled marksman with exceptional accuracy and vision.",
    answer: "Who is Hawkeye?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where the hero Peter Quill, also known as Star-Lord, searches for his missing father.",
    answer: "What is Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The villain in 'Avengers: Infinity War' who seeks to collect all the Infinity Stones.",
    answer: "Who is Thanos?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where the hero Carol Danvers, known as Captain Marvel, helps the Avengers in the fight against Thanos.",
    answer: "What is Avengers: Endgame?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where the hero Peter Parker faces off against Mysterio, an illusionist and master of deception.",
    answer: "What is Spider-Man: Far From Home?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character in Marvel movies who is a genetically enhanced super-soldier and leader of the Avengers.",
    answer: "Who is Captain America?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The organization in Marvel movies responsible for creating and enhancing superhumans, including Scarlet Witch and Quicksilver.",
    answer: "What is HYDRA?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where the hero Peter Quill discovers his true heritage and encounters his father, Ego.",
    answer: "What is Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The artifact that houses the Space Stone and allows characters to travel instantly across the universe in Marvel movies.",
    answer: "What is the Tesseract?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where the hero Scott Lang, also known as Ant-Man, joins the Avengers in the fight against Thanos.",
    answer: "What is Avengers: Endgame?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character in Marvel movies who is the Norse god of thunder and wields the enchanted hammer, Mjolnir.",
    answer: "Who is Thor?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The powerful artifact featured in 'Guardians of the Galaxy' that contains an Infinity Stone.",
    answer: "What is the Orb?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Marvel movie where the hero Peter Parker is mentored by Tony Stark and faces the Vulture as the main antagonist.",
    answer: "What is Spider-Man: Homecoming?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character in Marvel movies who is a genius billionaire, inventor, and philanthropist, known for his suits of powered armor.",
    answer: "Who is Tony Stark?",
    topic: "Marvel",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The first film in Christopher Nolan's Batman trilogy, where Bruce Wayne begins his journey as the Caped Crusader.",
    answer: "What is Batman Begins?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The League of Shadows, led by this character, serves as the primary antagonist in 'Batman Begins.'",
    answer: "Who is Ra's al Ghul?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The district attorney in Gotham City who becomes the vengeful villain Two-Face in 'The Dark Knight.'",
    answer: "Who is Harvey Dent?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The actor who portrayed Bruce Wayne/Batman in Christopher Nolan's Batman trilogy.",
    answer: "Who is Christian Bale?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The iconic vehicle used by Batman, equipped with advanced weaponry and technology.",
    answer: "What is the Batmobile?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The criminal mastermind known as the Joker, portrayed by this actor in 'The Dark Knight.'",
    answer: "Who is Heath Ledger?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The corrupt police officer in 'The Dark Knight' who plays a crucial role in the Joker's plans.",
    answer: "Who is Detective Jim Gordon?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The high-tech gadget used by Batman for gliding and soaring across Gotham City.",
    answer: "What is the Batwing?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The prison in 'The Dark Knight Rises' where Bruce Wayne is held and eventually escapes.",
    answer: "What is the Pit?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who serves as Bruce Wayne's loyal butler and confidant throughout the trilogy.",
    answer: "Who is Alfred Pennyworth?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The organization led by Bane in 'The Dark Knight Rises,' aiming to destroy Gotham City.",
    answer: "What is the League of Shadows?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The actress who portrayed Selina Kyle/Catwoman in 'The Dark Knight Rises.'",
    answer: "Who is Anne Hathaway?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The hallucinogenic flower used by the League of Shadows in 'Batman Begins.'",
    answer: "What is the Blue Flower?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The device created by Lucius Fox in 'The Dark Knight' to turn every cell phone into a sonar emitter.",
    answer: "What is the Bat-Sonar?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The League of Shadows plans to destroy Gotham City by releasing this into the water supply.",
    answer: "What is fear toxin?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The name of the criminal who kills Bruce Wayne's parents, motivating him to become Batman.",
    answer: "Who is Joe Chill?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The psychiatric hospital where the Joker is held in 'The Dark Knight.'",
    answer: "What is Arkham Asylum?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The mountainous prison in 'Batman Begins' where Ra's al Ghul trains Bruce Wayne.",
    answer: "What is the League of Shadows' training ground?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The actress who portrayed Rachel Dawes in 'Batman Begins' and 'The Dark Knight.'",
    answer: "Who is Katie Holmes?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The powerful villain in 'The Dark Knight Rises' who wears a mask to alleviate constant pain.",
    answer: "Who is Bane?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The underground criminal mastermind in 'The Dark Knight Rises' who goes by the alias 'John Blake.'",
    answer: "Who is Robin?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The weaponized microwave emitter in 'Batman Begins' used by the League of Shadows to vaporize water.",
    answer: "What is the Microwave Emitter?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The female ninja and love interest of Bruce Wayne in 'Batman Begins,' a member of the League of Shadows.",
    answer: "Who is Talia al Ghul?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The actor who portrayed the Scarecrow (Jonathan Crane) in Christopher Nolan's Batman trilogy.",
    answer: "Who is Cillian Murphy?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The fictional city in which Christopher Nolan's Batman trilogy is primarily set.",
    answer: "What is Gotham City?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The vigilante symbol used by Batman to strike fear into the hearts of criminals.",
    answer: "What is the Bat Signal?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The criminal who, in 'The Dark Knight,' creates chaos and mayhem as an agent of the Joker.",
    answer: "Who is Two-Face?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The actor who portrayed the character of Bane in 'The Dark Knight Rises.'",
    answer: "Who is Tom Hardy?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The prototype armored suit used by Batman in 'Batman Begins,' prior to the creation of the iconic Batsuit.",
    answer: "What is the Prototype Batsuit?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The secret organization revealed in 'The Dark Knight Rises' to have manipulated events in both previous films.",
    answer: "What is the Court of Owls?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The theme of the criminal underworld being inspired by symbols and theatricality runs prominently in this Nolan film.",
    answer: "What is The Dark Knight?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The name of the ice-breaking ship featured in 'The Dark Knight Rises' as part of Bane's plan.",
    answer: "What is the 'The Iceberg'?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The iconic villain in 'Batman Begins' who uses fear toxin to induce terrifying hallucinations.",
    answer: "Who is the Scarecrow?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The specialized vehicle used by Batman in 'The Dark Knight' for urban pursuit and evasion.",
    answer: "What is the Batpod?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The district attorney in 'Batman Begins' who is a close friend of Bruce Wayne and later becomes Two-Face.",
    answer: "Who is Harvey Dent?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The opera-themed criminal mastermind in 'The Dark Knight' who wears a distinctive makeup mask.",
    answer: "Who is the Joker?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The real name of the character who becomes Batman's ally and eventually takes up the mantle of Nightwing.",
    answer: "Who is Dick Grayson?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient and mystical organization that trains Bruce Wayne in martial arts and combat in 'Batman Begins.'",
    answer: "What is the League of Shadows?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The female cat burglar in 'The Dark Knight Rises' who becomes both an ally and love interest for Batman.",
    answer: "Who is Selina Kyle?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The powerful hallucinogenic flower used by the League of Shadows in 'Batman Begins.'",
    answer: "What is the Blue Flower?",
    topic: "Batman Trilogy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The school of witchcraft and wizardry where Harry Potter learns magic.",
    answer: "What is Hogwarts?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The dark wizard who killed Harry Potter's parents and tried to conquer the wizarding world.",
    answer: "Who is Lord Voldemort?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical sport played on flying broomsticks in the wizarding world.",
    answer: "What is Quidditch?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The three-headed dog guarding the trapdoor that leads to the Philosopher's Stone in 'Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone.'",
    answer: "What is Fluffy?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical creature that serves as the postman in the wizarding world.",
    answer: "What is an owl?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The platform at King's Cross Station where students board the Hogwarts Express.",
    answer: "What is Platform 9¬æ?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical object that allows wizards to travel through fireplaces.",
    answer: "What is Floo Powder?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The school subject taught by Professor Snape that involves the brewing of magical potions.",
    answer: "What is Potions?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The sport played on broomsticks with four balls and multiple goal hoops.",
    answer: "What is Quidditch?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical creature that serves as the guardian of the Triwizard Tournament's golden egg.",
    answer: "What is the Hungarian Horntail?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical candy that allows the consumer to experience different flavors and sensations.",
    answer: "What are Bertie Bott's Every Flavor Beans?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The object that allows Harry to view memories by diving into a pool of liquid.",
    answer: "What is the Pensieve?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical creature that serves as the messenger for the wizarding bank, Gringotts.",
    answer: "What is a Gringotts Goblin?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The dark wizard imprisoned in Azkaban and is the primary antagonist in 'Harry Potter and the Prisoner of Azkaban.'",
    answer: "Who is Sirius Black?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The spell that is used to summon an object to the caster's hand.",
    answer: "What is Accio?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical plant with a scream that is fatal to those who hear it, featured in 'Harry Potter and the Mandrake.'",
    answer: "What is a Mandrake?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical creature that serves as the mascot for Gryffindor house.",
    answer: "What is a Gryffindor Lion?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The enchanted map that reveals the layout of Hogwarts and the location of people within the castle.",
    answer: "What is the Marauder's Map?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical object used by Harry to communicate with Sirius Black in 'Harry Potter and the Goblet of Fire.'",
    answer: "What is the Two-Way Mirror?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical creature that Harry encounters during the Triwizard Tournament's second task, known for its song that rescues him.",
    answer: "What is the Mermaid?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Hogwarts house known for valuing ambition, cunning, leadership, and resourcefulness.",
    answer: "What is Slytherin?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical object that allows its possessor to become an Animagus, enabling transformation into an animal at will.",
    answer: "What is a Animagus Talisman?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical plant that can be used in potions to bring someone back from the brink of death.",
    answer: "What is the Mandrake?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The dark magical creature that guards the entrance to the Chamber of Secrets.",
    answer: "What is the Basilisk?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question: "The spell used to create light from the tip of a wand.",
    answer: "What is Lumos?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical device used to store and review memories in 'Harry Potter and the Half-Blood Prince.'",
    answer: "What is the Pensieve?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ghost who is the house-elf advocate and founder of S.P.E.W. (Society for the Promotion of Elfish Welfare).",
    answer: "Who is Nearly Headless Nick (Sir Nicholas de Mimsy-Porpington)?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical creature that guards the entrance to Gryffindor Tower, requiring a password for entry.",
    answer: "What is the Fat Lady?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical object that grants invisibility to the wearer, passed down to Harry from his father.",
    answer: "What is the Invisibility Cloak?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question: "The spell used to erase memories from a person's mind.",
    answer: "What is Obliviate?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical creature that serves as the messenger for the wizarding newspaper, The Daily Prophet.",
    answer: "What is an Owl?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical device used for storing and transferring thoughts, memories, and emotions.",
    answer: "What is a Pensieve?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question: "The sport played on flying broomsticks in the wizarding world.",
    answer: "What is Quidditch?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The wizarding village where Hagrid buys Harry his first wand and introduces him to the magical world.",
    answer: "What is Diagon Alley?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical creatures that pull the carriages that transport students from the Hogwarts Express to Hogwarts Castle.",
    answer: "What are Thestrals?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical plant that screams when pulled from the ground, used in potions in 'Harry Potter and the Mandrake.'",
    answer: "What is a Mandrake?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The magical creature known for its ability to detect when someone is lying.",
    answer: "What is a Boggart?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The spell used to disarm an opponent by forcing them to release whatever they are holding.",
    answer: "What is Expelliarmus?",
    topic: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The main character who tells the story of how he met his children's mother in the TV show 'How I Met Your Mother.'",
    answer: "Who is Ted Mosby?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who is Ted's best friend and often uses the catchphrase 'Legendary!'",
    answer: "Who is Barney Stinson?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The woman Ted pursues for most of the series, whom he eventually marries.",
    answer: "Who is Tracy McConnell?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Canadian singer-songwriter who appears as a fictionalized version of himself throughout the series.",
    answer: "Who is Robin Sparkles?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The bar frequented by the main characters, where much of the show's action takes place.",
    answer: "What is MacLaren's Pub?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The couple who marries early in the series and becomes the group's stable and committed pair.",
    answer: "Who are Marshall and Lily?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The company where Ted, Marshall, and Lily work during the earlier seasons of the show.",
    answer: "What is Goliath National Bank?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The mysterious woman with a yellow umbrella, often teased as the future mother of Ted's children.",
    answer: "Who is The Mother?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The playbook filled with schemes and strategies for picking up women, used by Barney Stinson.",
    answer: "What is The Playbook?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The holiday invented by Barney Stinson, celebrated by exchanging humorous or awkward gifts.",
    answer: "What is Slapsgiving?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question: "The actor who portrays Ted Mosby in 'How I Met Your Mother.'",
    answer: "Who is Josh Radnor?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The barista who becomes an important character in the later seasons, dating Ted and others in the group.",
    answer: "Who is Cindy?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who constantly struggles with commitment and is known for his womanizing ways.",
    answer: "Who is Barney Stinson?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The food item that Lily often uses as a metaphor for her relationship with Marshall.",
    answer: "What is the 'Olive Theory'?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The group's favorite hangout spot, known for its comfy couch and eclectic decor.",
    answer: "What is MacLaren's Pub?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The video resume that becomes a running joke throughout the series, showcasing unusual skills.",
    answer: "What is Barney's Video Resume?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The quirky news reporter and anchor who becomes a love interest for both Ted and Barney.",
    answer: "Who is Robin Scherbatsky?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The phrase used by Barney to describe an agreement where no questions are asked about a friend's questionable actions.",
    answer: "What is 'Bro Code'?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who is known for her artistic talents and becomes an art consultant.",
    answer: "Who is Zoey Pierson?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The doppelganger theory, introduced in the show, suggests that everyone has one of these somewhere in the world.",
    answer: "What is a Doppelganger?",
    topic: "How I Met Your Mother",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who was once fat but lost a significant amount of weight, leading to a dramatic transformation.",
    answer: "Who is Monica Geller?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The job title of Chandler Bing, which is often a source of confusion for his friends.",
    answer: "What is a Statistical Analysis and Data Reconfiguration?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The roommate of Joey Tribbiani who becomes a love interest for Ross Geller.",
    answer: "Who is Janine Lecroix?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who has an identical hand twin and shares this unique talent with the world.",
    answer: "Who is Joey Tribbiani?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who believes that everyone has a 'lobster' ‚Äì a soulmate destined to be together.",
    answer: "Who is Phoebe Buffay?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The animal that Ross Geller famously tries to teach his son, Ben, about through a song.",
    answer: "What is a dinosaur?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The famous catchphrase often used by Joey Tribbiani when expressing his approval.",
    answer: "What is 'How you doin'?'",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who has a well-known hatred for Thanksgiving, stemming from her childhood trauma.",
    answer: "Who is Rachel Green?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The soap opera character played by Joey Tribbiani, who becomes a cultural phenomenon.",
    answer: "Who is Dr. Drake Ramoray?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The science fiction movie that Ross Geller claims to hate but is later revealed to be a huge fan.",
    answer: "What is 'Star Wars'?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The reason why Phoebe Buffay believes in the existence of her deceased mother's spirit in a cat.",
    answer: "What is her mother's reincarnation?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The 'holiday' created by Chandler Bing, where participants must exchange homemade gifts of equal value.",
    answer: "What is 'Christmas In Tulsa'?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who briefly dates Rachel Green, believing that she is his daughter.",
    answer: "Who is Danny?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The soap opera character played by Joey Tribbiani that dies but is later resurrected with a brain transplant.",
    answer: "Who is Dr. Drake Ramoray?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The reason why Chandler Bing dislikes Thanksgiving, leading to his childhood nickname.",
    answer: "What is his parents getting divorced on Thanksgiving?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The sport that Ross Geller unsuccessfully tries to teach his son Ben, leading to a humorous incident.",
    answer: "What is rugby?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who mistakenly throws a woman's wooden leg into a fire during Thanksgiving.",
    answer: "Who is Joey Tribbiani?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The unusual item that Joey Tribbiani purchases to decorate his apartment but ultimately hates.",
    answer: "What is the ceramic dog?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The play written by Joey Tribbiani and performed by the group, featuring a character named Vicram.",
    answer: "What is 'The Last One'?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The song that Ross Geller sings to his daughter Emma to make her laugh, showcasing his dinosaur knowledge.",
    answer: "What is 'She'll Be Coming 'Round the Mountain'?",
    topic: "Friends",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The main character, a college dropout with a photographic memory, who begins practicing law at Pearson Specter.",
    answer: "Who is Mike Ross?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The brilliant and ruthless managing partner at Pearson Specter, known for his photographic memory.",
    answer: "Who is Harvey Specter?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The name of the high-powered legal firm where most of the series' action takes place.",
    answer: "What is Pearson Specter?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who is a senior partner at Pearson Specter and mentors Mike Ross.",
    answer: "Who is Jessica Pearson?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The legal secretary at Pearson Specter known for her sharp wit and strong personality.",
    answer: "Who is Donna Paulsen?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The firm that Harvey Specter and Mike Ross initially work for before joining Pearson Specter.",
    answer: "What is Pearson Hardman?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The firm's name after Jessica Pearson leaves and the name is changed.",
    answer: "What is Pearson Specter Litt?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The name of the legal clinic where Mike Ross worked before joining Pearson Specter.",
    answer: "What is the Manhattan Legal Services Clinic?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who is a junior partner at Pearson Specter and has a complicated relationship with Harvey Specter.",
    answer: "Who is Louis Litt?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The legal secretary at Pearson Specter known for her encyclopedic knowledge of the law.",
    answer: "Who is Rachel Zane?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The law firm that becomes a rival to Pearson Specter, led by Daniel Hardman.",
    answer: "What is Pearson Darby?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who is Harvey Specter's close friend and psychiatrist.",
    answer: "Who is Dr. Paula Agard?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The law firm that Harvey Specter briefly leaves Pearson Specter to join in Season 5.",
    answer: "What is Specter Litt Wheeler Williams?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The rival attorney and love interest of Harvey Specter, known for her sharp legal skills.",
    answer: "Who is Dana Scott?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The legal clinic where Mike Ross worked before joining Pearson Specter.",
    answer: "What is the Pearson Specter Legal Clinic?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The name of the legal firm where Louis Litt becomes a named partner.",
    answer: "What is Litt Wheeler Williams?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The law firm that acquires Pearson Specter in the later seasons of the series.",
    answer: "What is Zane Specter Litt?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The law firm where Rachel Zane works as an attorney before joining Pearson Specter.",
    answer: "What is Pearson Specter?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who is a senior partner at Pearson Specter and has a complicated history with Harvey Specter.",
    answer: "Who is Daniel Hardman?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The law firm that merges with Pearson Specter in the later seasons of the series.",
    answer: "What is Rand, Kaldor, Zane?",
    topic: "SUITS",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The U.S. Attorney for the Southern District of New York, who is a major antagonist for the character Bobby Axelrod.",
    answer: "Who is Chuck Rhoades?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The hedge fund manager and main character, known for his aggressive and unorthodox investment strategies.",
    answer: "Who is Bobby Axelrod?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The firm founded by Bobby Axelrod, specializing in hedge fund management.",
    answer: "What is Axe Capital?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The psychologist and performance coach hired by Bobby Axelrod to work with his employees.",
    answer: "Who is Wendy Rhoades?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The district attorney and Chuck Rhoades' wife, who has her own political aspirations.",
    answer: "Who is Wendy Rhoades?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The company that Taylor Mason works for after leaving Axe Capital, specializing in impact investing.",
    answer: "What is Taylor Mason Capital?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The name of the restaurant owned by Bobby Axelrod, where important business meetings often take place.",
    answer: "What is The Spartan-Ives Ice Cream Company?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The billionaire venture capitalist and tech guru who becomes a major player in the series.",
    answer: "Who is Taylor Mason?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The law firm where Chuck Rhoades works as a partner before becoming U.S. Attorney.",
    answer: "What is Sacker and Sacker?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The name of the company founded by Taylor Mason after leaving Axe Capital.",
    answer: "What is Mason Capital?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The name of the fund created by Bobby Axelrod and Taylor Mason, focusing on socially responsible investments.",
    answer: "What is the Axelrod Mason Impact Fund?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The billionaire investor and business magnate who is a major antagonist for Bobby Axelrod.",
    answer: "Who is Mike Prince?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who is the Chief Operating Officer at Axe Capital and later becomes a partner at Taylor Mason Capital.",
    answer: "Who is Wags?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The tech company that Bobby Axelrod invests in during the early seasons of the series.",
    answer: "What is the YumTime acquisition?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The federal law enforcement agency that Chuck Rhoades works for as the U.S. Attorney.",
    answer:
      "What is the U.S. Attorney's Office for the Southern District of New York?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who is a trader at Axe Capital and later becomes a key player at Taylor Mason Capital.",
    answer: "Who is Mafee?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who is a billionaire venture capitalist and tech guru, later becoming a rival for Bobby Axelrod.",
    answer: "Who is Taylor Mason?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The financial journalist and editor-in-chief of the fictional magazine 'Dealbreaker.'",
    answer: "Who is Mike Dimonda?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The name of the organization founded by Wendy Rhoades, providing psychological services to the finance industry.",
    answer: "What is Rhoades Global?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The artist and gallery owner who becomes romantically involved with Bobby Axelrod.",
    answer: "Who is Lara Axelrod?",
    topic: "Billions",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The main character and leader of the Shelby crime family, known for his strategic mind and distinctive flat cap.",
    answer: "Who is Thomas Shelby?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The city in England where the Peaky Blinders crime family is based.",
    answer: "What is Birmingham?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The World War I veteran who is a key member of the Shelby family and serves as the family's enforcer.",
    answer: "Who is Arthur Shelby?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The organization that Thomas Shelby works with during the later seasons, involving espionage and political intrigue.",
    answer: "What is the British Government?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The crime family that serves as the main rivals to the Peaky Blinders in the series.",
    answer: "Who are the Italians?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The bar owned by the Shelby family, which serves as a front for their criminal activities.",
    answer: "What is The Garrison?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The name of the horse owned by Thomas Shelby, symbolizing his rise in status.",
    answer: "What is Grace's Secret?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The undercover agent who infiltrates the Peaky Blinders and becomes romantically involved with Thomas Shelby.",
    answer: "Who is Grace Burgess?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The IRA member and childhood friend of Thomas Shelby who becomes involved in the Shelby family's activities.",
    answer: "Who is Freddie Thorne?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Shelby family matriarch, who is fiercely protective of her children and family business.",
    answer: "Who is Polly Gray?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Shelby family member who serves as the accountant and is known for his love of literature.",
    answer: "Who is Finn Shelby?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who is the Inspector at the Birmingham Police and has a complicated relationship with the Shelby family.",
    answer: "Who is Chief Inspector Campbell?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Shelby family's legal advisor, who becomes romantically involved with Thomas Shelby.",
    answer: "Who is May Carleton?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Shelby family member who is a war hero and struggles with PTSD.",
    answer: "Who is Michael Gray?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Shelby family member who is the family's historian and serves as the secretary.",
    answer: "Who is Ada Shelby?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who is a Communist agitator and forms an alliance with Thomas Shelby.",
    answer: "Who is Jessie Eden?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Shelby family member who is the family's lawyer and often handles legal matters for the business.",
    answer: "Who is Aunt Polly?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question: "The Shelby family's blacksmith and explosives expert.",
    answer: "Who is Isaiah Jesus?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The organization that serves as the Shelby family's main adversary in the later seasons, led by Oswald Mosley.",
    answer: "What is the British Union of Fascists?",
    topic: "Peaky Blinders",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The mythical continent where most of the events in 'Game of Thrones' take place.",
    answer: "What is Westeros?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancestral home of House Stark, located in the North of Westeros.",
    answer: "What is Winterfell?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Iron Throne is located in this city, serving as the capital of the Seven Kingdoms.",
    answer: "What is King's Landing?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question: "The family motto of House Lannister.",
    answer: "What is 'Hear Me Roar!' or 'A Lannister always pays his debts'?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The nickname for Arya Stark's sword, given to her by her half-brother Jon Snow.",
    answer: "What is Needle?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The continent located to the east of Westeros, known for its rich culture and cities like Qarth and Meereen.",
    answer: "What is Essos?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The mysterious and ancient order tasked with guarding the Wall and protecting the realm from dangers beyond.",
    answer: "What is the Night's Watch?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question: "The direwolf is the sigil of this house in 'Game of Thrones.'",
    answer: "What is House Stark?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The continent located to the south of Westeros, known for its deserts and cities like Dorne and King's Landing.",
    answer: "What is Sothoryos?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Red Wedding occurs during this event in 'Game of Thrones,' leading to the downfall of House Stark.",
    answer: "What is the War of the Five Kings?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancestral seat of House Lannister, located on a rocky promontory overlooking the Sunset Sea.",
    answer: "What is Casterly Rock?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient and powerful house that controls the Vale of Arryn, known for its mountainous terrain.",
    answer: "What is House Arryn?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The city that Daenerys Targaryen liberates from slavery and makes her base of operations in Essos.",
    answer: "What is Meereen?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The capital of the Free Folk (wildlings) beyond the Wall in the North.",
    answer: "What is Hardhome?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The massive Wall of ice and magic that separates the Seven Kingdoms from the lands beyond.",
    answer: "What is the Wall?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The dragon skulls beneath the Red Keep in King's Landing belong to this now-extinct species.",
    answer: "What are the skulls of dragons?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The poisonous substance used to coat weapons and kill Prince Oberyn Martell during his duel with the Mountain.",
    answer: "What is manticore venom?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The order of assassins and face-changers from Braavos, known for their skill in discreetly eliminating targets.",
    answer: "What is the Faceless Men?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The mythical creatures that are said to have disappeared from the world but are rediscovered by Daenerys Targaryen.",
    answer: "What are dragons?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The noble house from the Stormlands that Stannis Baratheon serves as the head, known for its castle of Storm's End.",
    answer: "What is House Baratheon?",
    topic: "Game of Thrones",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The high school chemistry teacher turned methamphetamine manufacturer and main protagonist of 'Breaking Bad.'",
    answer: "Who is Walter White?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The former student of Walter White and small-time methamphetamine manufacturer, partnering with Jesse Pinkman.",
    answer: "Who is Todd Alquist?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The blue-colored crystal meth that becomes synonymous with the drug trade in 'Breaking Bad.'",
    answer: "What is Blue Sky?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The fast-food restaurant that serves as a front for Gustavo Fring's drug operation.",
    answer: "What is Los Pollos Hermanos?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The DEA agent and brother-in-law of Walter White, who becomes obsessed with catching the elusive drug lord known as Heisenberg.",
    answer: "Who is Hank Schrader?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The lawyer who becomes the legal counsel for Walter White and Jesse Pinkman, known for his colorful personality.",
    answer: "Who is Saul Goodman?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The private investigator and fixer hired by Saul Goodman to assist Walter White and Jesse Pinkman.",
    answer: "Who is Mike Ehrmantraut?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The drug kingpin and owner of Los Pollos Hermanos, who maintains a calm and calculated exterior while involved in the drug trade.",
    answer: "Who is Gustavo Fring?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The chemical element that Walter White is known for using in his methamphetamine production.",
    answer: "What is methylamine?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The DEA agent and partner of Hank Schrader, who becomes romantically involved with Jesse Pinkman.",
    answer: "Who is Steven Gomez?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The street name used by Walter White in the drug trade, later adopted by Jesse Pinkman.",
    answer: "What is Heisenberg?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The silent and intimidating enforcer in Gustavo Fring's drug operation, known for his facial deformity.",
    answer: "Who is Hector Salamanca?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The pink teddy bear serves as a symbol of the tragic events that unfold in 'Breaking Bad,' notably in this season.",
    answer: "What is Season 2?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The DEA agent who initially suspects Walter White's involvement in the drug trade but is later killed by Jane Margolis.",
    answer: "Who is Hank Schrader?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The car wash that becomes a money-laundering front for Walter White's drug money.",
    answer: "What is A1A Car Wash?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The first name of Jesse Pinkman's girlfriend, whose tragic death has a profound impact on him.",
    answer: "Who is Jane?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The event that serves as the catalyst for Walter White's descent into the criminal world of methamphetamine production.",
    answer: "What is his cancer diagnosis?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The character who is the wife of Walter White, initially unaware of his involvement in the drug trade.",
    answer: "Who is Skyler White?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question: "The first name of Walter White's son, who has cerebral palsy.",
    answer: "Who is Flynn?",
    topic: "Breaking Bad",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient wonder located in Egypt, originally built as a tomb for Pharaoh Khufu.",
    answer: "What is the Great Pyramid of Giza?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The iconic Roman amphitheater known for its gladiator contests and public spectacles.",
    answer: "What is the Colosseum?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The pre-Columbian city built by the Inca civilization, located in the Andes Mountains.",
    answer: "What is Machu Picchu?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The Hindu temple complex in Cambodia, known for its stunning architecture and intricate carvings.",
    answer: "What is Angkor Wat?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient city in Jordan, famous for its rock-cut architecture and water conduit system.",
    answer: "What is Petra?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The grand palace complex located in the heart of Beijing, China.",
    answer: "What is the Forbidden City?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The historical city in Turkey that served as the capital of the Byzantine Empire and later the Ottoman Empire.",
    answer: "What is Istanbul?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The massive temple complex in Rome dedicated to all the gods of ancient Rome.",
    answer: "What is the Pantheon?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient city in Italy, famously preserved in volcanic ash after the eruption of Mount Vesuvius.",
    answer: "What is Pompeii?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The historical palace complex in Spain, known for its distinctive Islamic and Renaissance architecture.",
    answer: "What is the Alhambra?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient Greek temple dedicated to the goddess Athena, located on the Acropolis of Athens.",
    answer: "What is the Parthenon?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient Mayan city in Mexico, known for its stepped pyramids and astronomical observatories.",
    answer: "What is Chichen Itza?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The medieval castle located in the Loire Valley, known for its distinct French Renaissance architecture.",
    answer: "What is Ch√¢teau de Chambord?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient city in India, famous for its well-preserved Great Stupa and ancient gateways.",
    answer: "What is Sanchi?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The historical mosque in Cordoba, Spain, known for its horseshoe arches and stunning architecture.",
    answer: "What is the Great Mosque of Cordoba?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The iconic stone circle located in Wiltshire, England, believed to be a prehistoric astronomical observatory.",
    answer: "What is Stonehenge?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient city in Jordan, famous for its rock-cut architecture and water conduit system.",
    answer: "What is Petra?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient city in Cambodia, known for its intricate stone structures and iconic faces carved into temples.",
    answer: "What is Angkor Thom?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The medieval castle located on the River Shannon, known for its well-preserved cylindrical towers.",
    answer: "What is Bunratty Castle?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient city in Peru, believed to be the capital of the Inca Empire.",
    answer: "What is Cusco?",
    topic: "World Monuments",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The French military and political leader who rose to prominence during the French Revolution and led several successful military campaigns during the Revolutionary Wars.",
    answer: "Who is Napoleon Bonaparte?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient civilization that built the Great Wall of China, known for its Terracotta Army and the Silk Road.",
    answer: "What is Ancient China?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The conflict that lasted from 1914 to 1918, involving many of the world's great powers and alliances.",
    answer: "What is World War I?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The period of cultural and artistic change in Europe from the 14th to the 17th century, characterized by a renewed interest in classical learning.",
    answer: "What is the Renaissance?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The leader of the Soviet Union during World War II, known for his role in the defeat of Nazi Germany.",
    answer: "Who is Joseph Stalin?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient civilization that developed in the Indus Valley, known for its advanced urban planning and sophisticated drainage systems.",
    answer: "What is the Indus Valley Civilization?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The document that was signed in 1215, limiting the powers of the English monarch and influencing later legal traditions.",
    answer: "What is the Magna Carta?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The period of territorial expansion and colonization by European powers, particularly during the late 15th to the early 20th centuries.",
    answer: "What is the Age of Exploration?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The political and social movement that emerged in the 18th century, advocating for individual rights, representative government, and the end of monarchy.",
    answer: "What is the Enlightenment?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient Greek city-state known for its military prowess, unique form of government, and contributions to philosophy and art.",
    answer: "What is Athens?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The treaty that officially ended World War I, signed in 1919 at the Palace of Versailles.",
    answer: "What is the Treaty of Versailles?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient civilization that emerged along the banks of the Tigris and Euphrates rivers, known for its early systems of writing and law.",
    answer: "What is Mesopotamia?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The influential ancient Chinese philosopher and teacher, whose philosophy emphasizes ethics, morality, and social harmony.",
    answer: "Who is Confucius?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The decisive battle in 1066 that led to the Norman conquest of England and the crowning of William the Conqueror.",
    answer: "What is the Battle of Hastings?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The organization formed in 1945 to promote international cooperation and prevent future conflicts, replacing the League of Nations.",
    answer: "What is the United Nations?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The leader of the Mongol Empire, who conquered a vast territory in Asia and Europe in the 13th century.",
    answer: "Who is Genghis Khan?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The political ideology that emerged in the 19th century, advocating for workers' rights and the establishment of a classless society.",
    answer: "What is Marxism?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The era in European history marked by a renewed interest in classical learning, exploration, and artistic achievements.",
    answer: "What is the Renaissance?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The ancient Egyptian writing system that used pictorial symbols and was deciphered by Jean-Fran√ßois Champollion.",
    answer: "What is hieroglyphics?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "The historic event in 1517 when Martin Luther is said to have nailed his '95 Theses' to a church door, sparking the Protestant Reformation.",
    answer: "What is the Ninety-Five Theses?",
    topic: "World History",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I was an ancient Greek philosopher, a student of Plato, and the teacher of Alexander the Great.",
    answer: "Who is Aristotle?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am a legendary English playwright and poet, known for works like 'Romeo and Juliet' and 'Hamlet.'",
    answer: "Who is William Shakespeare?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I was an Egyptian queen, the last pharaoh of Ancient Egypt, and known for my relationships with Julius Caesar and Mark Antony.",
    answer: "Who is Cleopatra?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am a famous physicist, known for my theory of relativity and the equation E=mc^2.",
    answer: "Who is Albert Einstein?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I was an American civil rights leader who played a key role in the American civil rights movement.",
    answer: "Who is Martin Luther King Jr.?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am an iconic figure in the world of computing, co-founder of Microsoft, and a philanthropist.",
    answer: "Who is Bill Gates?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am a legendary rock musician, known for my role as the lead vocalist of Queen.",
    answer: "Who is Freddie Mercury?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am a former South African president and anti-apartheid revolutionary, known for my role in ending apartheid.",
    answer: "Who is Nelson Mandela?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am a world-famous American inventor, known for my contributions to the development of the electric light bulb.",
    answer: "Who is Thomas Edison?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am an Italian polymath, known for my paintings, sculptures, and contributions to various fields like anatomy and engineering.",
    answer: "Who is Leonardo da Vinci?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I was a powerful queen of England, known for my long reign and the Elizabethan era.",
    answer: "Who is Queen Elizabeth I?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am a legendary martial artist and actor, known for my roles in movies like 'Enter the Dragon.'",
    answer: "Who is Bruce Lee?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am a famous American astronaut, the first person to walk on the moon during the Apollo 11 mission.",
    answer: "Who is Neil Armstrong?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am a French military and political leader, known for my role in the Napoleonic Wars.",
    answer: "Who is Napoleon Bonaparte?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am an influential figure in the field of psychology, known for my psychoanalytic theories.",
    answer: "Who is Sigmund Freud?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am an American business magnate, investor, and co-founder of Apple Inc.",
    answer: "Who is Steve Jobs?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am a legendary Indian spiritual leader, known for my teachings on nonviolence and civil disobedience.",
    answer: "Who is Mahatma Gandhi?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am a renowned American author, known for my novels like 'The Great Gatsby.'",
    answer: "Who is F. Scott Fitzgerald?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am an iconic American actress, known for my roles in films like 'Breakfast at Tiffany's.'",
    answer: "Who is Audrey Hepburn?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
  {
    question:
      "I am a groundbreaking scientist, famous for my theory of evolution by natural selection.",
    answer: "Who is Charles Darwin?",
    topic: "Who Am I?",
  },
];

export default seedquestions;

